NO ANIMALS WERE HARMED DURING
THE FILMING OF THIS PRODUCTION
Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com
Your escrows are secured, father.
These souvenirs which once belonged
to our ancestors...
... will be studied...
... infused...
... and eventually will turn into new
conquests and cities.
I know that I have more responsibilities
now.
I also know that I need to be more
diligent.
The night and the morning shall become
one.
From now on, inattention is illicit for
all of us.
My children.
My children!
Do we have your permission, Bamsı Bey?
You may come in.
Bamsı Bey?
Isn't he here?
He will be here soon.
Then we shall take a seat and wait
for him.
Stop.
Does Bamsı Bey even like you?
I wouldn't like to be rebuked by him.
Yes, he does.
I mean I suppose he likes us.
Bamsı Bey is indeed a hospitable person.
We shall wait and see.
Cerkutay!
What are you doing with those
swords, Cerkutay?
Put them away at once!
Greetings to you.
Thank you.
Greetings to you too.
You are indeed welcomed at this
time of night.
You may tell me the reason you are here.
Bamsı Bey.
Oh, mighty Bamsı Bey.
You don't know me.
However, I have never forgotten you.
And I just can't forget.
With deceased Ertuğrul Bey...
... you saved the life of my father.
I was a little child back then.
In order to save my life...
... you stood against a sword.
The mark of that sword strike...
... can still be seen on your neck.
I remember now.
I can indeed recall you.
Thank you. May you live long.
Please have a seat.
With your excuse, Bamsı Bey.
It's not a problem.
I remember you.
May his soul rest in peace, my Ertuğrul
Bey named you after Süleyman Shah.
Süleyman.
Thanks to Allah...
... we are now partners with the Kayı.
Dündar Bey is helping us.
From now on, when our Osman Bey leaves
for numerous battles and conquests...
... he won't have to think about trade.
How magnificent. I wish you good luck
and blessed profits.
However, may you never give place to
illicit profit in your business.
May you keep this Tent away from
illicit doings.
Alright?
Do you get it?
Don't worry, Bamsı Bey.
Cerkutay.
We shall offer something to our guests.
Tell me.
Would you like to drink ayran or sherbet?
To tell you the truth...
... it's impossible for them to
drink sherbet, my Bey.
Why is that, Cerkutay?
Why can't they drink sherbet?
I drank all the sherbet.
So you drank a full jug of sherbet,
Cerkutay?
I was a bit hot and thirsty, my Bey.
So I drank it all.
-You were hot?
-Yes, my Bey.
It's not important, Bamsı Bey.
While we are here, we thought it'd be
good to visit you.
If you say so.
May Allah make your way clear.
-Amin.
-Thank you.
Bismillahirrahmanirrahim.
Don't bother.
Thank you.
So that you won't drink anything, may
Allah make your way clear.
We ate a lot at the meeting.
Yes, brother, indeed we did.
Boran.
Are you thinking about your brother?
Tell me if you're thinking about
Head-Alp Göktuğ.
Yes, I am.
I wish he was here with us.
He doesn't even know that I'm about
to get engaged.
Oh, my Bey!
Welcome, my veteran Bey.
Thank you.
Who did you fight against, my Bey?
Don't ask, Gence Bey.
No matter how hard you train, fighting
for real is very different.
He who stands against you also
swings a sword, right?
They wanted to kill me.
From now on, I will be present at any
clash that will take place.
Don't you ever dare to leave without me.
Is sleeping has become illicit for
you, my Osman?
People have given us the honor to
serve, my Bala.
Besides, when we die, we will have lots
of time to sleep.
Dinner is ready, my Bey.
Thank you, my Bala.
May your hands do not see any trouble.
Allow me, my Bey.
Bismillahirrahmanirrahim.
My Bala.
You already have many things to do.
And soon you will become even busier.
You can get more helpers if you want.
No.
I need no helper when it comes to
serving you.
Serving you is not a burden but
honor for me.
With you permission, I'd like to open a
workshop for the poor in Söğüt.
What a wonderful thought.
What a wonderful plan.
By doing so, I'd also like to raise
skillful women.
Perhaps, with your permission.
May you take Hazal Hatun with you.
Why, my Bey?
After all, they wanted the Beyhood
so deeply.
They tried to play games on us.
We shall give them new tasks.
We shall give them new tasks in order
to prevent them being tricked by Devil.
We must answer to their mischiefs with
good intentions...
... in order not to end up like them.
As you wish, my Bey.
However, I'd like you to know that...
... if she goes beyond the limit, I will
punish her.
As long as you are fair-minded...
... you shouldn't worry about it.
Thank you, my Bey.
My Bey, also...
Also?
For our past's sake...
... I'd like to choose the Hatun for you.
My Bala.
My beloved Bala.
My rose.
Every believer has a unique challenge.
And this is the challenge of our love.
Whatever Allah leads to us, we shall
accept it the way it is.
The duty is yours, my Bala.
May God bless you all, loyal servants
of Jesus.
May God bless you.
Amen.
The feudal landlord of all Turkish
borders, fearless lord Ayos Nikola...
... is waiting for you.
Do I have your permission?
You may come in, Arslan Bey.
May your victory be blessed, Osman Bey.
You got our revenge from them.
You banished those heathens who tried
to take the Serhat region from us.
May you live long!
May you live long too, Arslan Bey.
With the grace of Allah along with
the strength and effort of our Valiants...
... we got rid of those heathens.
Take a seat.
How are you been doing?
How are the conquest preparations?
The Beys and Alps are gathering.
And the swords are getting sharpened.
Then, we shall help you too.
We can't wait like this while Geyhatu
is on his way.
I say we break down the wings of heathens
located near our borders.
Well said, Osman Bey. Well said.
Attacking is better than waiting for them.
However, we are not strong enough to
attack them right now.
Not all Beys are present at the moment.
If all of them were present, I'd tell you
to arm ourselves and combine our power...
... to destroy the army of Geyhatu.
This is the sole reason why I'm suggesting
breaking the wings of his supporters.
I suggest we kill the soldiers and
commanders of Mongols...
... who walk between the confidentials
and sacreds of our people.
To achieve this, we shall form an
Akıncı Troop with high tier Alps.
They shall be Valiant muslims.
These Valiants who will come from the
muslim regions...
... shall kill the best soldiers the
Mongols have.
In the end, the Mongols will never have
the time to rest.
When did you come up this plan, Osman
Bey?
You are dreaming of conquest non-stop.
That's not the case at all.
We are the community of our prophet.
What did our highness order?
To live the same day twice is a waste.
For that reason, we'll fight,
we'll dream...
... we'll struggle,
we'll trade.
And we will chat.
But our two days won't be the same.
An Islamic union with valiants
who swore for shahada...
... a group of man who swore
to destroy the enemy.
Isn't this the whole story?
Aren't a group of people enough?
How many of us were there in the battle
of Badr? In the battle of Uhud?
How many of us were there in
the conquest of Mecca?
Were we not a handful
in many other battles?
May I enter, my Bey?
Come in, Saltuk.
News, my Bey. Surrounding areas' Lords
will come together in İnegöl.
Nikola is preparing for a new crusade.
They want revenge, Osman Bey.
- Tell the Alps to prepare.
- As you order, my Bey.
Do you need support?
Your prayers are enough.
Our prayers are with you.
Our cause is big, our paths are long.
More effort is what we need.
Our hearts are big, our
brotherhood is eternal.
- Give us your blessings.
- Bless you.
Losing this battle does not
mean losing the war.
For example, every defeat is
another whip. More and even more!
Were you like this, mighty Ceasar?
That’s what I thought.
Antandros!
How’s your daughter?
She was ill. Is she okay?
Mighty Ceasar blessed my daughter.
Nikis!
Your wife knows
you’re cheating on her.
Here’s an advice.
Fear a lover’s anger.
How do you know that?
With the wife of your
closest commander. Is that it?
Be cautious of the pain of the dagger you
will have on your back once the time comes.
And, Pakimeres!
So, Pakimeres, were the trade deals you
made with the Turks enough for you?
As you know, trade and
war are separate, Nikola.
Osman, killed all the soldiers
our Empire sent their way.
He also wounded my friend Alexander.
Let me ask you a question, Pakimeres.
If it goes on likes this…
… can Osman also take your
heads and your castles?
Tell me.
Tell me!
- You’re right, Nikola.
- I couldn’t hear you.
We’re here to obey your orders.
Good.
Men! The dirty part of politics is over.
Poisonous power of the gold is also over.
There is one power now.
The power of battle!
The power of battling to death!
To death.
Osman Bey. Hatuns of Kayı made
it with passion and love.
Thank them.
How is it, Boran?
What is it for, my Bey?
The new banner of Kayı.
Crescent and arrow.
Symbol of the world’s order.
It shows the Turks’ way of battle.
The banner of resurrection.
Announcement of the new state
we will establish to the whole world.
Thank you, Osman Bey.
May my Allah bless it.
May our Tent be a beylic,
may our beylic be a state.
May our state be blessed, my Bey.
Inshallah!
Kulacahisar veteran Aygül Hatun.
Now, she'll be
the head of the women’s union.
May Allah bless it.
Osman Bey, you saw me fit, and
that made me happy.
You gave me a duty, and I’m proud of it.
We're always there with our
swords whenever you need us.
We’ll hit the enemy's armies
like the lionesses that we are!
Thank you.
A great duty awaits.
Being brave and strong aren't
enough, you need to be cautious.
You’ll be cautious.
You'll take care of each other.
Don’t you make a mistake.
Don’t worry, my Bey.
Boran!
You’re in charge.
As you order my Bey.
As for the duty…
- You’ll infiltrate İnegöl.
- As you order, my Bey.
Nikola is serving
a feast for the Lords.
He gathered all
the Lords for a big crusade.
Infidel! He doesn’t behave himself.
A dog is always a dog, brother.
How will we do that, my Bey?
Do you know Sarı Saltuk?
My Bey! How does a
valiant doesn’t know Sarı Saltuk?
You’ll enter the enemy's
lair with any tricks necessary.
My Alps! I want you
to decide for yourself.
I want you to think for yourself.
Because those who grow
a state, are the mature ones.
Once our army is huge, I want
the mature ones leading it!
For this reason, the duty is yours.
Prepare the operation.
And don’t embarrass me.
Don’t worry, my Bey.
We’ll strangle them in their own castles.
We must make our enemy understand that
they can’t even imagine beating us!
If you even try, then
we’ll take that mind out of your heads!
My Bey! We can enter it. But…
How will we exit, my Bey?
If you can’t,
you’ll be prisoners.
And you’ll get
a taste of shahada.
Thank you, my Bey.
The job is ours, my Bey.
Don’t worry.
Brothers! You may
not come back from this duty.
- Give your blessings.
- Bless you, my Bey.
Brothers!
My Bey.
Being a martyr is an honour.
But if we become prisoners,
we might never see you again.
We used to be like that
when we were young, Osman Bey.
You’re not old yet,
Abdurrahman Gazi.
I still need you.
No one else can do this.
No one will know where you
will go and what you will do.
Your secret is my secret, my Bey.
Thank you.
Abdurrahman Gazi!
We always need to be one stop ahead.
- May Allah Bless you.
- Bless you.
May Allah bless both Osman Bey and you.
May Allah bless you too.
Welcome, sister.
- Allah bless you.
- Enjoy your meal.
- May my Allah bless you!
- Thank you!
Mother!
- May Allah always be with you!
- Mother, wait!
Hafza Hatun! Please take care of this.
Come, mother.
Hand me the basket, sister.
May God protect you and
Osman Bey, Bala Hatun!
Amen, mother.
Mother. Take these so
you can cook at home.
May God help you.
- Wait. Yusuf Alp!
- Yes, Bala Hatun?
Help this lady take her supplies home.
- As you order, Bala Hatun.
- Thank you.
- I’ll get it.
- Thank you, mother.
Bala. Bala Sultan!
How nice of you!
Thanks to you, so
many people are fed.
Don’t say that, my Gonca.
Allah is the one who gives.
That’s my sister with a clean heart!
If my Sheikh saw
your efforts, he’d be so happy.
The father is a strong castle for a girl.
Oh how much I need him
during troubling times.
I can’t wait for him to
come back from hajj!
Inshallah, my Bala.
Father. I’m sad that my
mother still won’t talk to me.
Can you turn dough into wheat?
It doesn’t, but…
I know that just like every Turk…
… the sound of swords clashing
and horses running gets you excited.
But you weren't
raised to be an Alp.
Remember that these
lands also need wise men.
Besides, was all your
education for nothing?
Did you read that
many books for nothing?
Father! Can't one be both
an intellect and a warrior?
Of course one can.
But now, we need
intellects more.
Also, you haven't made
use of your education yet.
Yes, you have to.
This is where you will.
Remember. States are
found by the efforts of veterans.
But they survive
under the intellects’ lights.
Thank you.
Let’s go.
Brother! Osman Bey is giving
us duties so we can gain experience.
Look at what you do…
What did I do, Boran?
Can’t we ask questions to our Bey?
Brother. Where did
you grow that head of yours?
Let’s go, brothers.
Boran Alp!
Where do you go to?
- To hunt.
- Did Osman Bey give you news orders?
What are you talking about?
Boran Alp.
This hunt looks different.
That Boy will get himself into
trouble again. My God, protect him.
I said we’re going to hunt. No more
questions. We've got places to be.
So be it. Go.
Let’s go, brothers!
I won’t leave
you alone with this hunt.
Bayhoca!
He never listens!
Oh, Bayhoca!
Praise be!
Bala, my daughter. You called me
to help you for such a good cause.
Thank you, daughter.
It made me very happy.
Teamwork makes the dream
work, Hazal Hatun. Thank you.
But, just supporting
isn’t enough. I want you to help.
Of course I will!
As long as you want it.
Come on, Alps!
Take the goods down.
Thank you.
Bala Hatun!
May I?
Sure, Hatun.
I’ve heard that you
were helping the poor, Bala Hatun.
I brought some from
the supplies in my house.
If you allow me, I’d
like to hand them away.
Thank you, my beautiful
sister. Here, bring them in.
Praise be, Bala. More
and more people are coming to help.
Praise be.
Bala?
Are you okay?
I need to find a second
Hatun for Osman Bey, Gonca.
This topic again...
It's not about Osman
or me anymore.
It's the will of Ertuğrul Gazi.
What are you saying, Bala?
There can be no Bey
without a child, Gonca.
That's why I need to find it.
Bala Hatun, if you allow
me, I'd like to help.
To escape the Mongol's taxes,
the Turks sell their goods to you.
So, they can survive
thanks to you.
You're the reason new Tents
attack us with new Alps.
There are three paths they can
sell their good through.
Bursa, İnegöl, Constantinople.
All three of these roads
will be closed.
With your soldiers, not
only the traders...
... but also the shepherds,
the Turks in your bazaars...
You will hunt them down one by one.
If you forget that they need
to die because they are Turks...
I'll forget that you are Lords.
You know what comes after this.
War.
Not just war.
Blood, tears, and booty.
Men! All the booty you take will be yours
free of the Empire's tax.
You'll attack Osman
from three sides.
Until he can't breathe.
What happens when they
start attacking?
What happens?
You just close your castles' doors.
The rest...
... is my job.
I'll be with you with an army
larger than ever before.
Not just the Empire's army.
I'll crush them with an army
of Mongols and Cumans!
Any objections?
Good.
Then...
- Battle to death!
-Battle to death!
Good. Finally, we've
come to the point.
I like battling to death.
Men. You're my
guests for the night.
And remember. I don't consider you Lords
until you give me a tasbih made of Turks.
For Rome!
Who are you?
Get off the cart!
I beg you, don't kill us!
Help us! Isn't there anyone!
Help us!
-Help us!
Boran, sing us something.
Don't talk, just fight.
Isn't there anyone?
Help us! Help us, I beg you!
Help us!
-Who are you?
-We are poor musicians, sir.
We were going to Tekfur Nikola's
feast. Three Turks stopped us...
...they took our clothes
and instruments. Please, help us.
Put it there. Get the oil and
carry it there. Good.
-What's your name, woman?
-My name is Aksu. I live in Söğüt.
-Which family?
-My father is a trader.
We lost him early. We live with
what he has left.
-My mother and I live on our own.
-Mashallah.
Don't you have anyone else?
We don't, my lady.
With this beauty, why didn't you
marry already?
There were candidates...
...but let's say it was Allah's
decision.
There is goodness in everything.
Maybe fate will smile upon you.
I knew you would come, Aksu.
Come.
Have your family received
their every need?
-They have, my lady. Thank you.
-Not at all.
Thank you too.
Mashallah.
It fits you so well.
These are the gold coins
I mentioned you.
But my lady, what do you
want from me?
Aksu.
My pretty daughter,
from now on...
...you will be like my daughter.
But at first, no one will know this.
I will find you a good spouse.
But only if you do everything
as I say.
I owe you my life, my lady.
Order me to die and I will.
All right. I will make you...
...Osman's...
...Osman Bey's wife.
But there is an...
...al-Sirat bridge that you need
to pass.
So, Bala Hatun.
Thank Allah.
-I finished my job.
-Thank you, Hazal Hatun.
-I appreciate your help here.
-Of course, I will help you.
But you look sad?
Is there a person free of sadness?
We can talk later.
Of course, but don't endure
in silence, my daughter.
Hazal Hatun is always with you.
Thank you.
What's wrong, Cerkutay?
Is something up?
-My bey, am I not a warrior?
-You are, Cerkutay.
-Then why doesn't Osman Bey call me?
-He awaits me to name you ready.
My bey, what are you waiting for?
Cerkutay, do you remember the
words I taught you?
In my head--
In my heart.
If they are in your heart, repeat them.
I will control my hand, my tongue
and my waist.
I won't strike someone who yield...
...I won't pull my sword against women,
children and helpless. I know the rest.
I won't step back from a battle.
What's wrong, İdris Bey?
What are you looking at?
Doesn't your arm work anymore, Bamsı Bey?
İdris Bey.
İdris Bey!
Come on, alps, come on!
Be quick!
-We'll hang them in Kulucahisar and Söğüt too.
-Move aside!
My Allah! My Allah!
What is this? What is this?
What is this?
Hold on, uncle.
We'll find out.
Davud Bey!
What is this? What is this?
Where are our flags!
Our flags are here, Bamsı Bey.
-Did Osman Bey order this?
-Osman Bey ordered this.
-What kind of a thing is this?
-His tent is right there.
Go on.
Come on.
Open the doors!
Osman Bey.
Osman Bey!
Those flags... Our flag...
Why did they change?
Who did you talk to before
making such a decision?
No one! And the beys
don't allow it!
We came all this way under
that blue banners!
We found peace under its shadow,
we had dreams.
Now you can't change it, Osman Bey!
This flag is our common value.
You can't change it!
You should lower it at once. Or else
neither our beylig or your throne will stand.
I see that my beys are disturbed
by my actions.
I heard that...
...my position is threatened.
Under this holy flag, Kayı people
found peace.
They fought, it's true.
Dodurga Tribe also flies its own banner.
Salur Tribe also flies its own banner.
My ancestor Oghuz has 24 tribes.
And they all have marks.
Every tribe dreams for its own.
And every tribe builds its own
order.
Then, who will unite the separated
tribes of Oghuz Khan?
Who will bring them together?
Who will realize our dreams?
Who will say that we are brothers,
that we are of the same blood?
Who?
We will.
We will!
Osman Bey, we...
...are used to living under that
sky blue banner.
That flag is the legacy
of our ancestors.
This flag is the symbol of resistance
and resurrection.
We resisted with this flag and
we resurrected.
Now, we are on our feet.
Now, we will walk.
Now is the time of jihad.
Now is the time of the conquest.
Now, I will ask you a question.
What will destroy the Islam world?
Separation.
Disagreement.
Unrest. Laziness.
For this reason, I offer you to
unite all tribes under one crescent.
This is such a great
crescent that...
...the shadow of that crescent...
...will cover all the world.
Without discriminating the tribes,
we'll form a great state.
This country isn't only the country of
the Kayı but all the Turks.
It will be the country of the Islam world.
It will be the country of the oppressed.
Under this crescent, 7 regions and
72 nation will find peace.
All right, Osman Bey.
You are right.
You thought well.
But, Osman Bey, great dreams
end with sorrow...
...if they aren't talked about.
Now, if you don't include
us to your great dreams...
...you can't create a country
or do conquests.
Forgive me.
As long as I have valiants
who speak the truth, as you...
...no one can beat us.
Brother.
The sharpness of your mind made me glad.
Long you live, Osman Bey.
You didn't ashame...
...my Ertuğrul Ghazi.
Long you live, Osman Bey.
Long you live.
If you get disturbed by a decision
I make again, one day...
...don't give up on what you believe in.
After all, this tent will
be...
...the home of heart and mind.
Bamsı Bey.
Where do the most beautiful women
of Bithynia live in? İnegöl!
Where does the greatest commander of
Rome live in? İnegöl!
Play for Lord Nikola!
-Speak of the devil...
-Stay calm, friends.
Heroic commanders of Bithynia!
Where were you all this time?
We were expecting you earlier.
We came to turn our voice and
instruments into gold, sir.
If you are late, you should
entertain us first.
Tell me, my noble commander.
What's the name of your beloved one?
-Helena.
-Helena? Helena.
Helena...
Save me from this pain...
...I will die from my love!
Helena...
Helena!
Ohh, Helena...
I will come to your show
without coins.
Our show is our gift
to all the soldiers of the castle!
I guess you are lost in the castle.
I'm sure someone will give us a hand.
A room is prepared for the musicians.
Zülfikar will get you at night.
Now go to your room and wait.
-Boran Alp.
-Yeah?
Look at this? Our bey's spy
in the castle is a young girl.
It's me, Bayhoca.
-Bayhoca?
-What are you doing here?
I thought you would need me.
Oh, my dear friend! You are late.
We were waiting for you!
If you weren't Savcı Bey's son,
I would hang you here, Bayhoca.
-But I--
-My bey, when will you grow up?
Brother Boran, what will we do now?
-I want to throw him over the walls but...
-But I--
Silence. Silence. Don't talk.
Such a trouble-maker...
Pray to Allah that you carry Osman Bey's
blood. We have to protect him now.
To be honest, I admire your talent, sir.
We were raised by the holy pope,
'brother'.
His holy hands can disguise us in
any shape, 'thank Allah'.
But if we can't access the information
that Bamsı hides...
...his holy hands will introduce
us to death.
David is in the tribe. He is tracing.
He is after Bamsı. And after our last
blow...
...Bamsı lost all his power.
If needed, we'll organize a night
operation.
Tell David to get close to him
for 'healing'.
And get ready to drink his blood.
-Salam Alaikum
-Alaikum Salam.
Welcome, Dündar Bey.
Come, sit.
Thank you.
-Süleyman, let's order food for our bey.
-Right away.
What food, Melik Bey?
We are here to talk trade.
All right.
Are the goods gathered? Are the
caravans on the way? Tell me.
Dündar Bey, when it's about trade,
you don't think of anything else.
If I knew that there was a trader
like you in Söğüt...
...I would bring all my goods to here,
years ago.
Thank you. Thank you.
Better late than never.
From now, Söğüt will be the center
of trade.
-Inshallah.
-We'll trade with distand places.
Thank Allah.
-I should treat you with a cold ayran.
-Thank you. Thank you.
What is this?
It's your share, Dündar Bey.
We didn't put enough effort to earn
our share yet.
It's been just a few days.
We declared our intentions, my bey.
Therefore, the business has started for us.
If a trader is giving away coins
before the business starts...
...either they have
things to say...
...or they have a greater plan.
What's your intentions?
Or, in this lion's den,
the trader wants...
...to have an ally to trust
fully, Dündar Bey.
Of course, we made our deal
with Osman Bey.
But if something happens to Osman Bey.
Anything can happen to us here.
For this reason, my master Melik
wants to give this to you as a token.
Thank you.
You are a great helper, Süleyman.
If I had a helper like you,
I would rule all these lands.
-Inshallah, my bey. Inshallah.
-Inshallah.
Inshallah.
Come on now.
I should go.
Inform me when the caravans move.
Then we can talk about how we'll
carry the goods to far away.
All right, may Allah protect you,
my bey.
He is like a wolf in sheep's disguise.
If we dig a little bit more, we'll
take the wolf out of Dündar.
-Huh, 'brother'?
-Yes, 'brother'.
Don't get disturbed as you don't
know these things. He is tracing.
He'll spend the night in somewhere.
Where he is?
How he is?
Who knows.
Of course, he'll come.
Of course.
He doesn't want to leave his hunt
and return. That's how it is.
That's how it is.
Baysungur!
Find two alps who know how to trace.
They should search the hunting sites.
And bring Bayhoca if they find him.
As you order, my bey.
Eat now. Come on.
This is your room, go on.
Lord Nikola appointed this room for you.
If you have a command, tell us.
Good. I'd appreciate it if you bring me
wine at night, pretty girl.
I'll be in your service, sir.
Go on.
They are in their rooms.
I thought your mission to be a game.
Blame it on my youth.
I put Osman Bey's mission...
...and your lives in danger.
-Forgive me.
-My Allah! He is still speaking.
Bayhoca, you are young and brave...
...I see Osman Bey's fire in your eyes.
But to be like Osman Bey...
...you don't know how much
way you still have to go.
Baran Alp, I learn much from
you tonight.
Come on now.
-Welcome, Zülfikar.
-Thank you.
-He is a gift from our Sheikh.
-Who is this?
-Savcı Bey's son, Bayhoca.
He was passing by.
He wanted to ask how we fare.
Are the lords in their rooms?
This is where the lords' rooms are
There are four guards.
-You should control yourselves.
-Thank you, brother.
I will take you there safe and sound.
May Allah help you.
Come on.
Bayhoca, don't move anywhere. We'll
come and get you. We'll leave together.
As you want, Boran Alp.
May Allah help you.
Come on, brothers.
Gonca.
What are you thinking about?
I'm thinking about my mother, Bala.
My dear mother.
She made these with great care.
I wish, both she and my father...
My beautiful sister.
Who knows? Maybe Sheikh Edebali
will come to your wedding?
-Isn't he our father?
-He is.
After our alps return with victory,
we'll begin the wedding preperations.
Inshallah, Bala.
Inshallah.
The soup kitchen is good, right?
-It made the poor smile.
-It's really good, Bala.
I liked this Aksu Hatun.
She is a pretty woman.
She seems to have a good heart.
I say that we should put her into
a trial.
-If she succeeds--
-So, Bala?
What will happen then?
Then, I will talk to Osman.
I'll mention her.
Maybe he too will like her.
What are you doing here?
We came to tell lullabies to
the lords.
What will you tell us?
Death's sweet lullaby.
Take them away, brother.
Watch out for us. Come.
A trap, huh?
You weasels!
What did you put on
the dagger?
A few medicines.
You will see now.
Nikola!
Did you think this place to be a chicken
coop? Enter as you want...
...take what you want, is that so?
-You will die, dishonorable!
Attack! But don't kill.
What happened? Osman's fox!
Did the sheepdogs of the coon
hurt you? -You will die!
You first.
Take them to the dungeon.
We have a feast tomorrow.
Take him away.
-My brothers won't return before killing
them. -We came anyway, just in case.
They'll give up on their lives but not
return before killing them.
They have 4 lords.
They'll have more important missions
from now on. And about us...
...we have Nikola on our part.
Nikola will die tonight.
-All right, my bey.
-All right.
My bey.
Open it.
Eftelya, what happened?
They got caught, Osman Bey.
-They were taken to the dungeon.
-My bey, let's fire this dark night.
I pity us if we leave before taking our
brothers and killing these dogs.
Take us to the dungeon.
Do you know a way?
Thank you.
Eftelya, keep your eyes on Nikola.
Dishonorable dogs!
Enough!
From now, it's on us.
You are left to me from my father.
Protect yourself and
your daughter.
In return for your service, people will
live with justice and freedom.
I'll show it to the whole world.
This is the parole of Osman Bey
son of Ertuğrul Ghazi.
Give me your blessing.
Come on.
My bey, how could they get
caught?
I trust them completely.
We'll find out later.
-Give me your blessings.
-It's yours, my bey.
It's yours, my bey.
May Allah help us.
Let him go!
You ignoble dogs!
Let them go!
Did you hurt your hand, dog?
Let's see how strong you are!
My Bey, those are our guys.
They are alive, my Bey.
Let's go.
Osman Bey!
Kill Osman!
I am here Boran brother, hold on!
My Bey!
Brothers!
My Bey, what are you doing here?
I don't leave my brothers alone.
My Bey, forgive us.
We failed the duty.
Boran, tell me, how did you get caught?
Do we have a spy in us?
You got beat up to a pulp, Gence Bey.
They medicated us.
What happened Boran?
How did you get caught?
- Apparently, they waited for you here.
- I don't know my Bey, but Bayhoca...
What happened to Bayhoca?
Bayhoca was here when we arrived, my Bey.
What are you talking about?
He followed us secretly.
Just like your younger days, my Bey.
Let's get out of here before soldiers
find us, my Bey.
Let's go.
I think I know you.
Right?
These eyes, this look.
This jaw...
You must be very close to him as he
assigned you to this mission.
But I have not seen you with him before.
Tell me your name young man.
So you are going to keep your silence.
Now tell us who you are.
- Go to hell Nicola!
- Stop!
You are going to accompany me to there,
young man.
By the way we caught the alps who came to
raid us.
Do you know why?
Because of your clumsiness.
Search all the rooms!
Close the exits!
Search this one!
Why have not they arrived yet?
There's someone here ma'am.
Who are you?
What are you doing here?
I am a musician.
I drank wine a bit much.
You are coming from Bilecik, right?
I can sing you a lovely song.
Liar!
You are lying!
I wish I was dead.
I can't stand the sadness of a young man
like you.
Don't you worry. I am going to hang you
all with a great ceremony.
My uncle Osman Bey...
will make you pay for the blood you shed!
He'll ruin you all.
My uncle Osman...
Are you Savcı's son?
Lena's son...
Bayhoca, right?
Have you heard what I've heard, Vladius?
Nicola, we hit the bullseye, Nicola.
So these eyes, these looks...
You are that old chap's grandson.
Kill me.
Kill me!
Kill me, think that you won!
I am not in hurry, young man.
I am sure your uncle Osman will come
for you.
Even for a last time, right Vladius?
Bayhoca...
Let's see what your uncle Osman is
going to do!
My Bey, Bayhoca must be waiting for us.
He is not, Boran.
My Bey, what are you talking about?
- They caught him.
- No, my Bey.
Nobody realized him.
They caught him, then they realized
we are going to the governor.
They planned medicines and everything.
That's why Eftelye, Aruton and Zulfikar
knew everything.
Are we going to leave him here my Bey?
They won't kill my nephew.
Their aim is to get me.
Now we are getting out of the castle.
Then, we will come back and raid them.
- Eyvallah my Bey.
- Eyvallah.
It's been late, he is still absent.
Something bad must have happened.
They realised my son is a Kayı Bey.
They captured my son.
Maybe..
- Maybe...
- Lena Hatun.
Don't wory.
We'll find him eventually.
We'll hear from him eventually.
Our son will come back safe and sound.
Also, no one can dare to hurt him.
Who can hurt Savcı's son?
I'ld make them regret,
don't you know, Hatun?
What are you talking about Savcı Bey?
What am I going to do with revenge
if something bad happens to my son?
If they hurt him..
Lena... Oh Lena.
Find him Savcı.
Sir, Osman took the captives.
My valiant uncle, god bless him!
He was in the castle all the time!
I know where to find Osman, Nicola!
He'll come for his nephew!
Open the door!
First Kulucahisar, then my castle!
Do not I have soldiers to stop this man?
Can't we lock this man down!?
You are fine, thank God, Osman Bey.
They captured Bayhoca.
I saw them taking him to Governor's room.
I know. I know.
Take us back from where we came.
Wait for our sign.
I am going to be back for Bayhoca.
Find 'em!
- He went after Osman's alps.
- Enough, Hatun!
We are going to find him!
- Can I, my Bey?
- Come in, Baysungur.
Tell me what's new.
Osman Bey is waiting for you, my Bey.
Is there anyting about my son, Bayhoca?
Tell me.
Speak!
Speak up, Savcı Bey. Ask about Bayhoca.
Ask him what this is about!
Speak!
Tell me if it's about my son.
Is he hurt?
Enoguh Lena!
Enough.
It must be important.
Let's go to the tent.
My son, Bayhoca.
Osman Bey.
Is there anything about my Son?
Is my son fine?
Tell me Osman Bey, is my son fine?
Where is my son, Osman Bey?
Bayhoca went after my Alps to
Inegol Castle.
Didn't they realise that my son
followed them?
Osman Bey, what's my son's situation?
My Alps got caught.
- I saved them but...
- But?
My son Bayhoca?
Did you leave him there, Osman Bey?
You saved your Alps and sacrificed my son?
- Did you sacrifice my son, Osman Bey?
- Lena!
Enough already.
My Brother, where is my son?
What's his situation?
Tell me.
He got captured by Nicola.
No. No.
No he can't be.
No.
No way.
How can you leave my son Osman Bey?
How can you!
- Lena!
- How can you sacrifice my son, Osman Bey?
- Tell me!
Brother.
How can you sacrifice my young valiant,
Osman Bey?
My young valiant.
How can you leave him there with
the murderers, Osman Bey?
Tell me!
How could you?
Bayhoca is still alive.
How can you know that, ha?
- How can you know that?
- They won't kill my nephew.
They'll use him against me.
What if they kill him?
What if they kill my son, Osman Bey?
Lena!
He wanted to be Ghazi.
Ghazis end up with shahada.
You killed my son by leaving
him in the castle for once, Osman Bey.
But you killed my one thousand times.
You killed me one thousand times!
Shame on you!
Lena!
I wish you were the captive!
I wish you were the captive, not my son
Osman Bey1
My Bey, a messenger from the
castle came.
If you don't give Kulucahisar back...
I'll kill Bayhoca.
No!
Savcı!
Bayhoca...
Bayhoca!
If I return without my nephew...
My horse shall be my coffin.
My tent shall be my coffin!
If I don't keep my word..
Ertuğrul Ghazi's tent shall be my tomb!
Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com